<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicole Beholz</title>
    <description>Freelance support for ideation, concept development, project management, and process optimization.</description>
    <link>http://nicolebeholz.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 14:59:33 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 14:59:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kleinerdrei</title>
        <description>kleinerdrei is a place for everything that’s important in the first three years of life: It combines a concept store for ergonomic, environmentally-friendly and beautiful products with a wide ranged offer of courses for babies and parents and with a midwife practice.</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/12/kleinerdrei/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/12/kleinerdrei/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zweimeilenladen</title>
        <description>Zweimeilenladen is a pop-up store for local products and local production. It gathered the best products created within a two-mile-radius in Hamburg and Berlin, including coffee and chocolate as well as clothing and accessories, utensils for urban gardeners as well as books, bikes and beds. In addition, we hosted numerous events and workshops on local production and DIY.</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/11/zweimeilenladen/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/11/zweimeilenladen/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abhati</title>
        <description>Abhati combines Indian and Swiss herbology with Swiss technology for a new range of premium natural skincare products. A liquid soap called “One Hand Washes The Other” is its headline product. 50% of the proceeds are being passed on to buy toilets for schools in India. We developed branding and packaging and produced a crowdfunding video for it.</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/10/Abhati/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/10/Abhati/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Arjowiggings</title>
        <description>Arjowiggings is a leading manufacturer of creative papers. They asked Paperlux to reinvent the bookmark – and we did! The result is this playful 3D object which is able to mark a line or even a single word. </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/09/Arjowiggings/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/09/Arjowiggings/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Today I Made</title>
        <description>Today I made was an online platform to help people share the stuff they made. From April 2012 to April 2013 we collected crazy and unexpected, beautiful and helpful things – from small robots to amazing food, from clothes to web apps.</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/08/today-i-made/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/08/today-i-made/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hanse</title>
        <description>Hanse is an avant-garde fashion collection highlighting Hanseatic features, exclusive prints and draped shapes.</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/07/Hanse/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/07/Hanse/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
