<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicole Beholz</title>
    <description>Freelance support for ideation, concept development, project management, and process optimization.</description>
    <link>https://nicolebeholz.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 14:55:53 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 14:55:53 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kleinerdrei</title>
        <description>kleinerdrei is a place for everything that’s important in the first three years of life: From romper suits to first shoes, from shape sorters to baby slings. Ergonomic, environmentally-friendly and sustainable – and with a design that makes children and parents happy. kleinerdrei combines a concept store with a wide ranged offer of courses for babies and parents and with a midwife practice.</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/12/kleinerdrei/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/12/kleinerdrei/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Zweimeilenladen</title>
        <description>Zweimeilenladen is a pop-up store concept for local products and local production. It gathered the best products produced within a two-mile-radius in Hamburg and Berlin. The range of goods included coffee and chocolate as well as clothing and accessories, utensils for urban gardeners as well as books, bikes and beds. In addition, we hosted numerous events and workshops on the subject of local production and DIY.</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/11/zweimeilenladen/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/11/zweimeilenladen/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Abhati</title>
        <description>Abhati combines Indian and Swiss herbology with Swiss technology for a new range of premium natural skincare products. A liquid soap called “One Hand Washes The Other” is its headline product. The clou: If you buy this soap 50% of the proceeds are being passed on to buy toilets for schools in India that have none. </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/10/Abhati/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/10/Abhati/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Todayimade</title>
        <description>We built TodayImade to help people share the stuff they made. From April 2012 to April 2013 we collected crazy and unexpected, beautiful and helpful things – from small robots to amazing food, from clothes to web apps. Our motto was: It does not matter what you make. What matters is that you make stuff – so be proud of it!</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/09/todayimade/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://nicolebeholz.com/2016/07/09/todayimade/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
